Guide to the Kermit Carlyle Parsons papers, circa 1945-1999
Parsons, Kermit Carlyle papers, circa 1945-1999
- Series IV. Cornell University Faculty and Administrative Files
  - Art, Architecture and Planning (AAP) Administration
    - Annual Reports: College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1971/72-1979/80 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Annual Reports: College of Architecture, Art and Planning, 1971/72-1979/80 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence with Cornell President and Provost, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Center for Urban Development Research Search Committees, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Center for Urban Development Research Search Committees, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Library Committee, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Provost - Parsons Correspondence and Documents, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Equipment Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Annual Reports - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Notes Eastern Deans Meeting, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Reports and Correpsondence - Architecture Education, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Architectural Record Puerto Rico Committee, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - AAP Accreditation Files, October 1972 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Tenure and Promotion, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Phone Call Records, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Architecture Deans Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - College Correspondence - Faculty Notes and Enrollment Statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - US Planning School Policy Survey, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Finanal Title IX Regulation Implementing Education Amendments of 1972, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Dean Parsons Correspondence and Miscellaneous Papers, 1972-1978 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Dean Parsons Correspondence and Miscellaneous Papers, 1972-1978 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Architectural education reports, 1972, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - College Council Files, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - International Council of Fine Arts Deans - Notes and Correspondence, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - New York City - Tuskegee, May 17, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - American Institute of Architecture Convention - San Francisco, CA, May 7-10, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Various Architecture Education Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Various Architecture Education Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - College of Arts, Architecture, and Planning Faculty and Space Requirements, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Cornell Correspondence - Administrative, Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Billing Files, Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Summary of Invited Comments from Alumni and Professionals Outside the University to the Architecture Study Committee Report, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Governance and Direction, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Funding Statistics and Memoranda, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Responsibility Analysis, 1973-1974, 1974-1975, 1973-1975 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Johnson Museum Opening Ceremony Invitation and Museum Guide, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Annual Reports - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1973-1974 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - College Notes on Budgets and Space, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - College Notes on Budgets and Space, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Messick Correspondence, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - AAP Staff Directory and Budget Files, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - College Policy Correspondence and Articles, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - College Policy Correspondence and Articles, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - College Correspondence and Notes, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Student Statistics and Course Offerings, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Student/Curriculum Research for Budget Preparation, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - AAP Notes and Correspondence - Budgets and Conferences, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 1974-1975 Budget Files, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - 1974-1975 Budget Files, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Budget Files - Annual Report 1974, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - 1974-1975 Budget Memoranda and Files, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Program Descriptions and Needs, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Program Propsals, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Corporate Letters, 1974-1976 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Budget Financial Administration, Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Budget Files - Endowments and Salary Notes and Memoranda, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning Brochure, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Course Schedules, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - AAP Correspondence, Memos, and Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - 1975 Commencement Program, June 2, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Faculty Information and Budget Information, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - AAP memos and notes: appropriations, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Architecture Education Study Board Meeting - Washington, DC, May 29, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Architecture Enrollment Data, Spring 1975 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Faculty and Course Information at Top Planning Schools, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - 1975-1976 Budget Files, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - 1975-1976 Budget Files, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Budget Files - Statements of Account, Cost Saving Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Budget Files - Alumni Newsletters 1975, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - 1975 Annual Report to the President, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Memos and Messages from A. Lentini, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Equal Opportunity Legislation: Executive Orders and Guidelines, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1975; 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1975; 1979-1980 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Alumni Directory - Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Notes for Dean's Report, 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1975-1976 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - "Highlights / Annual Report - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning", 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Memo to the President, '1976 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - AAP financial notes and budget analysis, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Cornell Plantations Committee, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Cornell Plantations Committee, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Cornell Plantations Committee, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Cornell Plantations Committee, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Cornell Plantations Committee, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Cornell Plantations Committee, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Cornell Plantations Committee, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - AAP College Proposals and Studies, 1976-1979 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - "Architecture Among the Professions" Architecture Enrollment Study, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Eastern Deans Meeting - Cambridge, MA, January 19, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - "Responsibility Center Analysis, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - 1976-1977 Budget Files, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - 1976-1977 Budget Files, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Budget Files - Budget Preparation Files - FY 1976-1977, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Deans Council Meeting, April 20, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Budget Reduction Report, 1976-1978 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Annual Reports - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - College of Architecture, Art and Planning budget, 1976-1977 fiscal year, 1976-1977 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Cornell Washington DC Program Correspondence, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Budget Files and memos, 1977-1979 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Urban Development Articles and Correspondence, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Course Study Data, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Meeting with Provost Knapp, December 16, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 1977-1978 Budget Files, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Assembly, September - October, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - 1977-1978 Leave of Absence Files, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1977-1978 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - AIP school recognition program correspondence, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - College Meetings and Notes, 1977-2000 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Cornell Program in Washington, '1978 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Budget Guidelines and correspondence, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Deanship Correspondence, Articles and Notes, 1978-1980 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Deanship Correspondence, Articles and Notes, 1978-1980 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - AAP College Administration, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - AAP College Memos, Messages, and Mail, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Budget Material, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Budget Material, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Campus Mail, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Department of Landscape Architecture Files and Capital Budget Materials, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - College Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - College Budget Files, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Budget Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Budget Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Initial College Budget Submission, January 27, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning Finance Files, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Annual Report - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning Files, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Annual Reports - College of Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1978-1979 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - AAP Correspondence and Memos, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - 1979-1980 AAP Annual Report Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Arts and Architecture History Transcripts, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Department of Architecture Art and Planning Alumni Reunion, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Federal Assistance Applications, Curriculum Vitae, Budget Material, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Architecture Chairman Candidates, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Search Committee - Architecture Dean, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Washington Internship Program Correspondence, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Cooperative Education Program Files, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Cornell College of Architecture, Art, and Planning Brochure, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Newsletters and Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Budget and Programming Correspondence, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Meeting - Tokyo, Japan, June 1979 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Geographic Distribution of AAP College Alumni, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Articles, 1979-1991 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and College Highlights, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - AAP Budget Proposals, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Venezuela Trip, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - College of Arts, Architecture, and Planning Newsletters, 1980-1984 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Florida Trip - Richard Rose, Course Development, August 1980 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Annual College of AAP Report, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - CRP/AAP Brochures, 1980s (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Owings Professor Chair, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Parsons' Miscellaneous College Notes, 1982 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Cornell Plantations, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - National Endowments for the Arts Application, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Dean McMinn's Long Range Plan, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - "A Statement of Direction," William McMinn, April 2, 1988 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Dean MacMinn, Bowman Correspondence Regarding Stein Research, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Olive Tjaden Correspondence, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Cornell Real Estate Program Files, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Cornell Real Estate Program Files, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Historical Deans, Alumni Correspondence, 1994 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - City Visitation Report - Ft. Lauderdale FL - Tjaden, June 15, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Tjaden Hall Renovation Article, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Olive Tjaden Hall Files, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - William Henry Miller Building, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Dept of Architecture courses and notes, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Cornell's Second Century, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Cornell University Organization Discussion, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - "Readers Report", 1971 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Cornell University Announcements, 1971-72 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Urban Density and Quality of Life, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Cornell University Annual Report 1972-1973, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Cornell University Gift Reports, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Professional and academic correspondences, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Cornell University Budget, 1973-74 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Cornell planning conference - KCP info pack, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Parsons Employment Files, 1958-1977 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - KCP AAP Annual Reports, 1971-1977 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Cornell University AAP Announcements, 1976-77 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Application for recognition for Planning Education, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Planning journals and magazines, 1974-77 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Cornell University Financial Report, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Responsibility Center Analysis for 1975-1976, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - Berlin Program correspondence, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - performance appraisal schedule, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Affirmative Action Advisory Board, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Grant application for Cooperative Education Program, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Cornell in Washington Coop Education Program information network, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - Cornell in Washington student internship coordination, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - Cornell Landscape Architecture graduate program, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - Brochures and newsletters - Cornell and ULI publications, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - "Future Enrollments and Demographic Trends" Cornell University, April 1978 (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - Program in Urban and Regional Studies projects and proposals, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence regarding faculty position, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - Cornell Finances, 1974-1978 (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - Misc. Administration, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - AAP Memoranda, 1975-1979 (Box 95, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence regarding class admin and other projects, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 33)
    - Affirmative Action Advisory Board reports and correspondence, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence and docs regarding student resources and rights, 1977-78 (Box 95, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence and newsletters about AAP program, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 36)
    - Cornell AAP program development correspondence, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 37)
    - Docs regarding expanding the Cornell HPP program, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 38)
    - Technical Assistance Center proposal and correspondence, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 39)
    - Cornell news and AAP HPP program revision proposal, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence regarding University offerings in History of Art and Architecture, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 41)
    - Cornell AAP Announcements, 1973-79 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Cornell in Washington program information, 1975-1979 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Cornell Economic and Capital plans, 1978-1979 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Misc. correspondences, 1980s (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Grant documents, 1976-1983 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Grant documents, 1976-1983 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Cornell Newsletters and Reports, 1965-1985 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Cornell Newsletters and Reports, 1965-1985 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Cornell Newsletters and Reports, 1965-1985 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Cornell Newsletters and Reports, 1965-1985 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - AAP Annual report and other notes, 1980-85 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Cornell in Washington budget and correspondence, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Cornell-in-Washington report, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Academic Program Review at Cornell University, 1994-1996 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1966-1998 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Cornell-in-Washington draft report, undated (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Cornell in Washington Documentation, undated (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Planning for Cornell/Cornell Consulting
    - Medical Center Planning and Development, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Campus Planning Questionnaire (org), 1960-1961 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Statement on Lipschitz Sculpture and Libraries, October 1962 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Cornell Campus Planning: 1964-1965, 1963-65 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Cornell University Campus Plan - Architectural Study, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Cornell University Campus Architectural Study correspondence, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Cornell University Campus Plan - Notes, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - "Existing Conditions Evaluation" by Einhorn Yafee Prescott Architects, December 1988 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Cornell Campus Planning minutes and studies, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - "The Campus Plan - Precinct and Project Planning", January 1991 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Campus Landscape Design Notebook and Guideline, 1991-1992 (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - "Sage Hall Renovations Feasibility Estimate" Produced by Turner Construction Company, 7/1/1992 (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - Renovation of Sage Hall Cost Estimates, July 1992 (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - Sage College Presentation, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - Cornell campus planning committee minutes and reports, 1993-94 (Box 96, Folder 32)
    - "Communique - The Cornell Campaign", December 1994 (Box 96, Folder 33)
    - Sage Hall - Letters to Cornell Committee of Trustees, 6/1/1994 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Campus Planning - Sage, Lincoln, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Cornell Campus Planning documents, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Sage Hall Consultant Pricing -Tomlan, 9/1/1995 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Sage Hall Documents and Notes, January 1995 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Sage College - Historical Notes and Schematics, 1875-95 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Sage Hall Lawsuit: The Heritage Coalition, Barbara Ebery v. ILPC Ithaca Landmarks Preservation Commission, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Sage Hall Demolition - Letter to the Editor, March 1995 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Sage Hall and Historic Value, 1/10/1995 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Sage Hall / Sage College history, 1994-1995 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Carnegie Quarterly, Summer-Fall 1995 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Sage College Newspaper clippings, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Sage College Newspaper clippings, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Sage College Articles, notes, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - KCP Statement to Landmarks Commission and supporting materials, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Parsons Correspondence to Cornell Campus Planning Committee and Board of Trustees, Sage College history, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Parsons Correspondence to Cornell Campus Planning Committee and Board of Trustees, Sage College history, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Sage Hall - Legal Correspondence, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Sage Hall Affidavit, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Sage Hall Demolition Debacle Denouncement, August 21 ,1996 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - KCP statement and correspondence, 1993-96 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - KCP statement and correspondence, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Sage Hall Correspondence and articles, 1994-96 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Sage Hall Correspondence and articles, 1994-96 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Sage Hall Articles - Ithaca Journal, 1994-96 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Sage College Campaign, 1994-1996 (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Sage College - Board of Trustees Correspondence, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - News stories about Sage Hall project, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Parsons Letters Protesting Sage Renovation, 1993-96 (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - Plantation Documents, Spring 1996 (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - Sage College Files, 1996-1997 (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - Planning Accreditation Board self-study report, 1996-97 (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - Cornell Campus Development and Planning Files, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - Notes on Campus Planning Committee, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - Historical Survey of the Arts Quad, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - Cornell University Files, undated (Box 97, Folder 36)
    - Cornell University Ag Quad Area, undated (Box 97, Folder 37)
    - Cornell Campus Planning Files, undated (Box 97, Folder 38)
    - Photos and Architecture Drawings, undated (Box 97, Folder 39)
    - Sage Hall Legal Documents, undated (Box 97, Folder 40)
  - Coursework
    - Term papers, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Term papers, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Term papers, n.d. (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Term papers, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Term papers, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Term papers, 1961 - 1965 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Term papers, 1963 - 1964 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Term papers, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Term papers, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Term papers, 1967 - 1969 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Planning thesis, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - City Planning 714, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 715 / U. Renewal Causes of Blight and Concept of Renewal, (n.d.) (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Arch 715: Conservation and Rehab, 1949-1956 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - ARch 715: U. Renewal/ Corresp., 1958 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Arch 715: Urban Renewal Syllabus, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - 715: Urban Renewal / Bibliographies, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - U.R. / Admin. Org for U.B., 1955-1958 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - 715: Public and Private Financing in U. Renewal, 1956-1959 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - U. Renewal Seminars/ O Winston, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - UR 1959 / Syllabus and STD Research Topics, 1959-1960 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Urban Renewal / New York State, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Arch 715/ Urban Renewal (Winston), 1961 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Arch 711: 1. Functions of planers, planers as profession, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Arch 711: 2. Legislative Basis for Plg., 1958 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Arch 711: 4. Administrative Organization for Planning, undated (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Arch 711: Population Estimates and Forecasts, undated (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Arch 711: Lectures, 1958-60 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Arch 711: Reading Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - BPA 218 Municipal Administration, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Academic Group Projects, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Academic Group Projects, 1953 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - The Neighborhood and the Neighborhood Unit, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - Planning 710 Street Systems, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Planning 710 Street Systems, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Course binder, 1957-1958 (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Location and Growth of US Cities Lecture, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Arch 710: Introduction and Misc. KCP lectures, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - Arch 710: Syllabi, etc., 1953-1959 (Box 99, Folder 27)